Charlie, at the 44th of May this date on number 2 is invocation by Pastor Fortisonville God Church Rayne Fiseau.
I'm a thanks for being here!
We're honored to be here right now...
Let's go back with her
Heavenly Father we thank you very much for your incredible applause through Jesus Christ
It should have been stated upon our country up in This City
Replayed by our city council and I think that it gives us wisdom every decision
To keep ahead from their families or jesus
we pay for our businesses,
you would practice with them Lord.
You'd be causing more to be blessed
and thank your Lord for our military
that protects us here in around the world
We pray they keep Your hand up protection upon Him
And Be With Their Famous Sword where They Are
Thank For Your Grace That He Give To You So freely
May I Should Bless This Even?
Thanks Of The Poverished of In American
and To Serve You With All Our Hearts
In Jesus Name Amen
Amen
You Would You Leave The Poverished of In American?
I pledge allegiance to the flag
Of United States and America
And To Serve You With All That For Wich It Sands
One Nation, Unified
Invisible
with Their Teas Justice for All Our
Thank you Neil
But
I'm gonna throw His Son of Gender
Stop He's Recommending
Islands 6-210
Father Consenna Genda
If there are no questions
We have a motion to approve please.
Motion
by 13 and the second
Okay, the
6-210
Second pull call please
Johnson
Oh,
If you item number 11 is if
Reem will try saying engineering for professional
Design services to relocate state highway 1235 water main
On an EOSHOW River
Chuck, thank you man
As most of
You know, ODOT is has plans to re-ability the bridge over in
The OSHOW River as part
We have a existing water main on there
we talked about putting it back
On the bridge and
Design fee for doing that
And staff looked at
That option versus
The board underneath the river
It's our recommendation that we go with
Option of Born beneath
And then
We have an engineering firm to help us
To do design
To get permits
To helps
With a construction
Observation and bidding
Also,
We also had new rail in
In this south west part there
Chuck, I believe that you brought this recommendation before the council
Several months ago
Recommending
The boring and it's just kind of saying here is
To actually form a contract in
For those services
Correct
This for design engineering firms to do
Yes
Okay questions of Chuck
We would like to add something
Since Chuck has done this work
We have found out
Especially during the last flood that we had around Christmas time
That's in pictures of
The sewer main
It comes over
Over there, over here
Over from south part
To our sewer plant
And again
Over a number
A lot
We have heard who was doing high water levels during this last flood
So he provided us the photos
Were taking a look at it because
It's very isolated area
I've asked Chuck to take a look
This as well
And while
Well, if we think that going
To be economically feasible
If you may
Take an example of a change order
Something
That might add
Especially since we have a company in here
They would be already operational to
To take care of that
We might even economy and scale it doing so
If not, you'll still need
As the separate item
It's something
For this city for 40-50 years
Many times as high water events
I think there is something
That will start boring
Making sure
So i just wanted
To put that into the record
That we are working on
And it will be bringing you back options in the
Not too distant future
So do We currently have a lift station out there
Or this required
The addition of an lift station
There is an existing lift station
This was part of town
That pumps sewage across
A train bridge
In two to waste our treatment plant
Looking at
Water line goes over the Niel show river
Putting that underneath and aboring
At a different location of water main
But as Dean mentioned, you know
Hopefully we can get the timing to these together
So some economies scale out there
If they are boring, under any therever
I didn't want You To be surprised
We bring it back because later agenda
Add them so i wanted
That up for your information
This point in times to happen
We are connecting for asking
For approval of the design services
Contractor agreement
Correct, that's correct, Mary. Do we have a motion
Let me give you a second place
Question
Johnson
Thanks Chuck
Anything on your business team?
No not all this agenda
Anyone else staff reports or in Your packet
If You Have Questions to Ask the Vatable
And I would entertain Most To Jones to the ShUA Vatable
No doubt that's right
For approval?
Johnson, Kristen
Aye
We might do it in a pause for a minute